organicdeals.com 2016-05-30

# PRIVACY POLICY — Organic Deals

## Privacy Policy:

Organic Deals respects your privacy. Your use of this site, in any and all forms, constitutes an acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

 **Personal Data:  
** Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Organic Deals.

If you have entered a giveaway and are the winner, the e-mail and or address you provide may be sent to the company in order for them to fulfill your prize.

 **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act:**

This website is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

 **Log Files and IP Addresses:  
** We automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet). We use IP addresses to help us administer our site and collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. None of this information is linked to anything that could identify you personally. 

 **External Sites:**  
Organic Deals is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

 **Cookies:**  
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Organic Deals & Coupons to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Organic Deals does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie:  
** Google, a third party vendor, uses the DART cookie to serve ads. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google's Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

 **Amazon Affiliates Cookie:  
** Amazon Affiliates, a third party system, uses cookies to serve advertisements and links to products on Amazon.com.  You may read more about Amazon Affiliates and their [Operating Agreement here](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/gp/associates/agreement?ie=UTF8&pf_rd_t=501&ref_=amb_link_84018271_6&pf_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&pf_rd_p=&pf_rd_s=assoc-right-1&pf_rd_r=&pf_rd_i=assoc_join_menu).

 **Skimlinks Affiliate Cookie:** We use a 3rd Party to enable skimlinks affiliate partnerships. You can read their [Privacy Policy](http://skimlinks.com/privacy-policy#users) and find more information on [the cookies they use](http://skimlinks.com/user-cookies).

 **Facebook Social Plugin:**  
Organic Deals uses the Facebook Social Plugin. Please see [Facebook's Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other#socialplugin) for additional information and to read how you can opt-out. 

 **Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Organic Deals and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Organic Deals have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

The contents of this policy may be altered at any time, at our discretion. For any other information, please email the [the blog owner](mailto:susan@organicdeals.com) .

Last Updated: May 10, 2012
